Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to my
$3.5 million house tour. Let's go.
Oh my god, I'm just playing with them
now. Yeah. Oh my god, what you say?
Loud. Yeah, I can't respect it. I'm in a
gym, but I am not flexing. Came from a
Ford, I'm trying. I told him I'm next.
So, this house tour is very well
overdue. And I actually am not supposed
to be living here. I think I've been
living here for like 9 months. And we're
actually moving out next month because
we're getting kicked out of this [__]
place. Association does not approve of
our lifestyle. Clearly, we don't follow
the rules here. And again, I'm very
clean. I'm very bougie. But dude, I have
15 cars. It's bound to happen. Who the
[__] wants to put a little ass grass
patch like that right there? Like, how
does that even make sense? I hate
associations, and I'm never living in
one ever again. So, I've I didn't get to
put the house to the max on how I wanted
to. I would usually deck the house out
how I did with the other one and even
better now. But since I saw myself
living here shortterm, I don't really do
much to it. So, kind of like our driver
right now. I want to show this because
living in an association having this, I
get charged a $50 ticket every single
day just for having this here. My
standup jet ski. So, I have a leg in the
back and at the end of this video, we're
going to actually ride this into the
lake cuz we're going to get kicked out
of here anyways. So, what more does it
get another ticket of 500 bucks and do
what nobody's done in this neighborhood?
10 hour drive right now. The max we've
been able to fit is what, like eight
cars? Nine.
So, we we've been able to fit in one
line.
Yeah. Four.
Four cars.
Four.
One could go here if we really want to.
And we have two small cars. Two.
Six.
Two. Two more here.
One one there and one there.
Yeah. So, max like nine cars we've been
able to fit here.
And it's like playing Tetris.
Also, this is a $100 ticket right here.
Oh, yeah. Every single day I get a $100
ticket for just having this parked here
because the association does not approve
of having these cars parked here. So
when the guy comes and he writes a
ticket every single day, this is me
right here as he passes by. All right,
so welcome
to my house. So now before we go in,
keep in mind it's myself and Sebastian
behind the camera living here. So we are
two savages, two men living in this
house by ourselves. No women and
cleaning ladies that can't even keep up
after our [__] So keep in mind this is
as good as it's going to get. All right.
So soon as you come in through the door,
you are greeted by our friend the
astronaut. So if you guys saw the last
house tour, he was with us as well and
he is still somewhat intact which is
actually pretty cool.
I don't think he was there for the last
house tour.
Yeah, he was, bro.
He was there at the end.
Yeah, I don't think he was part of the
house, but we got him in the other
house.
Yeah,
this took like 2 months to come in and I
bought it. It was like $10,000. Then you
have one of my favorite
Harley-Davidsons. It's like weird. It
like even turns it on.
They're old school. You got to shake it,
you know. Bet they love this [__]
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Never give up. You never give up.
Come on.
What was that? I have no idea.
really catch
the whole house smells like [__] gas.
All right, carbon dioxide by the time we
finish this video.
So, walking over here, this board, we
actually had it up over here on this
wall, but like I said, since we're
moving, one of the first things that
came off, then I have nowhere else to
put it, so I put it right there. This is
kind of like my every single day area.
pull up here, get my keys, my wallet,
my other key that I have to take daily
with me. And um the most memorable
moment that we probably had this year,
or most not memorable, more memorable
ones, most iconic and irreplaceable
moment was this right here, streaking
the Super Bowl. So, we even got sent the
actual Super Bowl passes that we did
when we streak the Super Bowl after we
left jail. And these are the these are
the shoes that I use in this same
picture right here. So see the shoes
right there. Crazy fast. I'm [__]
crazy fast. This smells like fuel, bro.
Holy [__] In here is the menace's room.
Sebastian.
Oh, okay. Okay. You know what?
Round of applause. Usually whenever I
come in here, I have to like go like
this and like jump over the bed. Okay.
Okay. Approved. I like nice taken care
of.
I even have my trade history up there.
What the [__] is this, dude?
Trades I've taken there in London.
What is this, brother? Oh no.
Oh no. I approve of that.
Profitable.
Look, this guy even [__] pretends
like he's reading a book. He organizes
colog. Okay. Hey, I approve. I like
that. So, this is Seas's room. Right.
Right outside here we have our kind of
game room, table tennis area, ping pong,
whatever you want to call it, or the
garage. This is kind of like our game
area. We never really used it. Usually
whenever we do poker nights, put this
table up and then we'll play with the
poker table. Put it here in the middle.
We actually got a Mike Tyson signed
boxing glove from the Lantern himself.
Shout out to Jordan for gifting that to
us. Got a dart board right here, which
bro, like I'm so nasty, dude. Like I
dude, I literally pull up and I know I
centered that [__] and I know I centered
that. I didn't even have to look at
that. I I I actually thought that was me
right now. I was like, "What the fuck?"
So, this is like So, I like using
certain areas of the house as like pure
memorabilia. And in the other house that
I have, I'm going to have just a whole
room dedicated to just trophies of
legendary [__] like this. This is my
drift car door. So, my first drift car I
ever had, when I sold it, this door came
off as I was drifting it, test driving
it with the guy, and I'm like, "Bro, let
me stay with the door. It means
something." Signed by all my students in
the event that I gave away the laminer.
So, again, this is irreplaceable. Can't
get this again. This is my first
computer. This is the first computer
that I made a million dollars on. So, I
kind of retired it after I made a
million and now it's here. And then up
here is my first laptop that I made my
first $100,000 on. So, it's kind of like
retired right there. Now, the monitor
that I used for the live stream turning
100 into the mill that is no longer in
function. We're going to add to the
bottom of this, which is going to be
where we turn 100 into a million and
where we've made $10 million in trading.
So, it's like every single time we hit a
big goal like that, we retire the
equipment, put on a wall, set another
goal. So, massage chair. We I I think I
used this five times this whole year. I
never really use it. Fire extinguisher.
We're equipped with this because you
never know when you might [__] need
it. So, this is kind of my living area.
One, very small, very cozy. I like it a
lot. We have our dining table. And then
that head over there. If you weren't
part of the live stream when we were
turning the 100 into the middle, you
might be confused on what that is, but
after watching this clip here, you'll
probably understand.
So, this kind of where we eat dinner
sometimes with the team. And then we
have the famous set and forget toilets.
Now, if there's one thing I'm going to
miss from this house compared to the
other one, it's going to be these
toilets. My god. Oh, wait. This is
actually really dirty. Can you see how
dirty the floor is before we go in?
All right. So, these toilets are
legendary. Check this out. Ready? Open
sesame.
Walking out here, we have my very tiny
backyard.
I call it tiny cuz you compare it to the
backyard that I have now. And this is
nothing compared to this. So, we used to
have a TV here, but we were hit with a
hurricane and the TV flew off. So, now
we have no TV here. We're going to put
it back on before we move out. Little
cool barbecue section that we have over
here. Done some parties here. It's very
chill. Um, little dining table. And then
this, I really like this. I'm not going
to lie. I really enjoy this lake view
because it gives you a sense of like
Phoenix. Yeah. You can kind of just look
at it. You know, you can't really do
nothing else other than look at it and
every once in a while we get the the
iguanas that pull up and then we'll
either chase them or kick them out of
here. If there's one thing that I'm
going to miss from the whole entire
house, it is going to be this. I wish I
had a lake in the back of my house. Now,
but I have so like literally the the lot
size of my whole entire house right now
is the size of this whole lake. So, I
have about an acre and a half in my new
house. And by the end of this video,
we're going to get the jet ski and we're
going to throw it in here and we're
going to ride it. And all these [__]
neighbors are going to send a demand
letter to kick me out of here. And this
is just going to be me riding the jet
ski
there. You know, get it. Oh, and by the
way, I think I forgot to mention the
person who lived in this house before
was an I don't know if the English
community knows who it is, but it's like
the bad bunny, but like smaller. And he
lived in this house for about a year.
And I found out when I moved in because
the cameras that were in the house, I
somehow got access to it. Me being nosy,
I'm like, "You know what? Let me see who
was in here." And the first thing when I
click is Ano's big ass face just like
looking at the camera, like setting it
up. I'm like, "Oh shit." And if you look
at this spot right here, like literally
this same sofa and then the railing and
the leg and the houses. I'm going to pop
up the picture of him here with his
family when he lived here for about a
year. So, it's kind of sick that I'm
able to live in the same house as him.
All right, so coming back into the house
is now the kitchen area. So this is my
little So I don't know if you guys know,
but I'm 6'2. You guys may be wondering
how the [__] is Alex 6'2? Well, dude,
cuz I get on this [__] every day and I
stretch myself and I grow half an inch a
week by just doing this, flipping myself
around and I just start reading. I read
a book for 30 minutes like this. That's
how I got in taller. Now, if you're a
short king, get you one of these
contraptions and trust me, the ladies
will love it. Here we have my little
tablet. I control the whole house
through this thing right here. Very
creative password.
Just like that, you're in. You know,
this is just for people inside the house
that want to turn on the Wi-Fi, but the
music, TVs, everything is controlled
through this. So, my kitchen, which is a
little bit of a mess. Don't want to show
too much of it cuz it's not like I'm not
messy, but I don't really spend much
time here other than just trying to cook
something up and it never works out. And
this is where we usually have like our
meetings if we don't fit in my office.
And then over here, oh my F1 car, which
by the way, I'm going to wrap this like
the company colors. I don't like this
red. I'm going to do something very cool
and custom very soon. By the time we put
into the other house, wherever I figure
out how to put it, we're going to color
combo board, which is going to be sick.
Then we have the queen's corner. If you
can notice, she's not so happy with me
right now. She is clearly like not even
paying attention to me. So, you can give
cat the house of her life. The toys, the
food. This is how they treat you. Look
at this.
Where the [__] is the money? Huh? No,
no, no. Talk to me over here. Where's
the money? Where? Where is the money?
Moving along. So, this is one of my
secret entrances. By the way, we have
like two rooms in the house that we
can't show simply because they're like
confidential. This is one of my hideout
spots. I bet you didn't know this was in
here. a little kind of pantry looking
thing. But when I close the door Oh
[__]
Diddy comes out of
All right, moving our way upstairs. We
have my Christmas tree. So, I've had
this Christmas tree since the last
house. Christmas tree. Um, this year I
wasn't focused too much on Christmas. I
was focused more on the whole entire
house. That I have had it the last
house. And clearly it looks different
because my cat decided to use it as a
toy. Now she's eating it all up. Going
up the stairs, we have uh first thing is
a beautiful view of all of our vehicles.
When this [__] is full of like nine
cars, it looks super sick. It looks like
those pages of cars that people put my
gold's dreams. Yeah, we have it, which
looks pretty sick. So, let's start off
with my master bedroom. On our way here,
we have a mirror. So, when the trades
come in through London session, they
look at themselves before going in and
they'll be like, I'm [__] up. And
then they just go in, you know.
And by the way, no. Right. I have
cameras out the whole house. There's a
camera right there. So they can't say
they didn't approve of entering the
market on the entry here. They done
[__] up. So I was going to clean up my
room. Am I right? You know what? Let's
leave it as authentic as possible.
That pink and blue thing is not my
pillow. That is not me. That is last
night's trade. They left it here. Okay.
That was the
the marking the territory. the the
market left liquidity there, right? So,
it's kind of my master bedroom. I'm
going to actually show you what my
morning routine is looks like, right?
So, every single morning, I'll be here.
I'll be laying down, whatever. When I
wake up, my alarm goes off at 5:30 a.m.
I'll get up,
look at the trade, we either hit take
profit or stop loss, whatever it ended
up happening. We wake up,
come in through here,
open our door, and we stand here.
Here we go.
Who am I [__] today?
Who am I going to [__] today?
By the way, I I actually have I actually
have night vision. So, usually like I
am, ever since I got robbed, I am a
little paranoid freak. So, I have 25
guns throughout the whole house and I
have night vision in every room. So,
don't want to pull up on me at night
time. [__]
I see you. I see you. So, have that
there just in case. So, I actually
really like this bathroom. You never
know. I'm in the middle of a shower and
should be getting kind of hectic out
here. You know, we we [__] ready. We
not [__] around. Just letting you
know with the laser and everything. So,
say hello to my little friend. Ready to
catch it. Ready? Set.
There you go. One more. There you go.
One more. Yeah. Come on.
Wait. I didn't see that.
One more.
So this is
my room. This is uh the guest section.
So for our London trades, we leave them
with their own toothpaste, their own
deodorant, their own toothbrushes that
they can pick from and hydration just in
case. So there's no excuses. We have
over here my this is my area. This is my
air purifier and humidifier. So I
usually like take it. So I have a steam
room in here by the way.
This little blue button over there is
like a steam thing and this whole room
turns into practically like a sauna. And
this kind of like takes out all that
water vapor which is pretty sick. This
is my
open.
All right. Over here we have my closet.
Ready?
This probably one of my favorite
closets. Sadly you guys can't see this
area here. It's blurred out. I'm sure
you guys know why. So besides that area
have an arsenal here. just in case. Oh,
we ready. We got [__] ready to go
every single time. I have no enemies. I
just like the freedom America gives you
to be able to do what the hell you want.
This is actually for iguanas. So, the
these are my shoes. I have a [__] ton of
shoes, which I probably use only like
five of them. And all of these I only
use these from now on. I have a I have
pretty much every single color way they
have and every single different spec. In
here we have my safe.
Not much in here. It's just a decoy. My
real safe is that one over there. Little
one. So they'll come in here, spend an
hour trying to break this. They open it.
There's just baby oil in there and a
dildo. You just done [__] yourself
cuz the real one's that one.
Or is it? Oh, and by the way, I have
this weight here because for whatever
slick women is like, "Oh, you're so
tall. your height. Like, oh yeah, get on
the scale. Get on the scale, you fat
piece of economy short, huh? Huh? Get on
the scale. How much you think I weigh?
How much do you guys think I weigh? So,
I'm going to prove to you guys that I'm
6'2 right now. Do you think somebody
that's 5'2 would weigh 200 lb? No. Look,
it's a real scale. Warm it up, right?
Look. Look. Let's put it in the in the
middle so people don't think anybody's
getting on it. Look, for real. I step
back. So you see right
193.
If I was 52 lb weigh 193, I'd be a
[__] bowling pin. How much do you
weigh? Let me see.
Let's see.
Get on the scale. Get on a scale, son.
Look at that. And this guy's the same
height and this guy. And I'm taller than
this guy.
Well, not right now. All right. So,
making our way out of here,
we have a beautiful overview to the
downstairs area. Now, we have your room,
your office, which used to be my studio,
but I saw this guy who was working in
the table. I'm like, you know what,
brother? Here, man. You deserve this. He
got my office. He got my studio and
turned it into his office. Classically,
a mess cuz I'm missing a table. You're
right. You know what? Fair enough.
Oh, there you go. So, this used to be my
studio where I would do YouTube videos
and tutorials. And this is where I did a
piece of the set and forget strategy
course inside of here. And aside from
that, this is where SA spends 90% of his
day. Over here, we have another room.
We We can't show them this room.
It's a room full of nothing.
It's full of nothing here, right? Yeah,
we can't show them this room. Let's just
leave that room how it is. Beautiful
views to the whips and beautiful views
to the outside which I absolutely love
the diversity. Now I could only show a
piece of this room. This is the famous
set and forget calendar is where we turn
the 100 into the mill. Literally week 1
week 2 week 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13
14. And then these are kind of like the
results that I've had throughout the
whole entire year. I really like this
and I'm going to try and take this paper
off and take it to the to the other
house. And now we are in the famous set
and forget office which I don't think
needs an introduction. I believe every
sing one of you guys have seen this
office. We've done the 100 to the mill
series in here. We've done many trading
tutorials. We've done many so much stuff
has gone inside this office. This is
where I usually spend 90% of my day. And
I love it because we have the beautiful
view outside. You can have a clear view
of you know who's driving by the
weather. I love this floor to ceiling
roof. And then this is also good because
I usually have the AC like a 69 68. So I
love this because this is my my barber
station. So this right here where I'll
sit down. Very cool. So then right here
we have my cold plunge which truthfully
I think I've used it 10 times. I hate it
because where it is right now there's a
lot of wind. Wind accumulates through
here because we have the roof and wind
kind of just accumulates comes in
through here and it splashes here and
then we're freezing. So, in the new
house, I'm going to put this outside
with the sun so I can actually be able
to use it to the max to my ability
instead of just leaving it. Going on,
brother. So, yeah. Aside from that,
this is uh it's my home. Next home is
going to be Yeah, it was my home. Well,
we're still here now. We're going to
move sometime next week. We'll be in the
house by the week after that. And uh
trust me, it's going to be a lot more
lit. This house is cool. A lot of people
came to this house. A lot of students, a
lot of great memories. And I love every
home that I live in. This one just kind
of random because the last home I got
robbed and I had to have a quick move
and this was just the first thing that
was available and I just grabbed it. Now
we decided to get the other one which is
a lot better. So you guys want to see
more house tours like this and you want
to see maybe a little bit more in detail
of everything, let me know in the
comments below and we'll do it. If you
guys want to let me know what I should
add to the house or what was your
favorite thing of the house, let me know
in the comments below and you know we'll
do crazier stuff with it. But all I can
say is the next house is going to be
absolutely crazy. Everything that we
were limited to doing here because of
the association and the community that
is gone now. Now we have freedom. And I
don't know how good that is. I don't
know if that's
there's no laws between our walls.
I think that's um
not safe for the people that live next
to us, which is only one neighbor. I
don't even know if I should be saying
that. But what I do know is that I
appreciate you guys watching this video
all the way to the end. Make sure to set
and forget. Hit that like and subscribe
button and I'll see you guys in the next
one.
It might be easier if we just carry it.
Bro, carry it and then let's carry it
back.
That's clearly the problem.
What if you just break that off?
[Music]
That did something, huh?
Yeah.
All right.
Yes, sir.
We're good.
Little engineering. You know, I I
actually studied engineering when I was
in college and they didn't teach me
this.
[Music]
All right. All right. Let's go.
I finally started jumping. What a day.
Swear to God I need it. Now I can't
afford to wait. I just had a fan hit me
up from Kuwait. Told him this would
happen and we not a minute.
Hit me for the rain.
It's one time when I'm looking at a face
up.
I think you broke it.
What?
overheating.
You think
that shit's pretty quick. I can't even
lie.
It didn't seem quick,
huh?
bro. I was only going like 10% throttle,
then it just died.
Yeah, it's like overheating.
We check for coolant. No, no, it's
definitely overheating, bro.
I smell it.
Hold on. Hold on. Take it out.
We don't stop. This is for going to
carry the boats.
It wasn't that bad.
This wasn't that bad.
On the low like I'm pushing out the
base. Told them come down and I'll meet
them at a gate. Got a check and I buy
myself a place. They get some money and
they blow it on, babe. I don't flex, but
I'm pushing all the weight. Told them
all I swear I got is what it takes.
Just like that.
Thank you very much.
I hope
one of these is yours.
Son and forget.